UAW Public Review Boaard Decisions 6094
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UAW Public Review Boaard Decisions
1996-1999
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW)
United Auto Workers (UAW)
Public Review Board
6094
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
5794420
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 10, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 19, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Automobile industry workers -- Labor unions -- United States; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America.; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America --Archives.
5794420
- Case #1215-1224, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Case #1205 - 1214, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Case #1205-1214, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Case#1183-1192, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Case#1172-1182, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Case #1161-1171, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Case #1151-1160, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Case# 1140-1150, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Case #1128-1139, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Case #1259-1268, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Case# 1249-1258, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Case# 1236-1248, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Case #1225-1235, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)